Hey there, it's the ghoul school!
Scooby-Doo and the Ghoul School is a animation, family, tv
movie film directed by Charles August Nichols.
Scooby, Shaggy and Scrappy are on their way to a Miss Grimwood's Finishing
School for Girls, where they've been hired as gym teachers.
Once there, however, they find that not only is it actually an all-girl school of famous
monsters' daughters but there's a villainess out to enslave the girls.
Shaggy Rogers / Mirror Monster (voice), played by Casey Kasem.
Scooby-Doo / Scrappy-Doo (voice), played by Don Messick.
Ms. Grimwood (voice), played by Glynis Johns.
Sibella Dracula (voice), played by Susan Blu.
Tanis the Mummy (voice), played by Patty Maloney.
Elsa Frankensteen (voice), played by Pat Musick.
Scooby-Doo and the Ghoul School is a 1988 animated comedy horror television film produced by
Hanna-Barbera for syndication as part of the Hanna-Barbera Superstars 10 series.
It is the second full-length film in the Scooby-Doo franchise.
The film was followed by Scooby-Doo!
and the Reluctant Werewolf in 1988, with the five girl
ghouls making their return in the OK K.O.!
Let's Be Heroes episode "Monster Party" in 2018.
The film explores themes of vampire, mummy,
werewolf, military academy, cartoon dog.
The tone is mind_bending.